// The initial data may be set here.

//Define own data, use example data or set data to empty array. 

//export const Data = [];  // An empty array must be returned at the least.

export const Data = [{"deckID":1,"deckName":"JavaScript","cards":[{"question":"Method to insert element in front of an array?","answer":"Array.prototype.unshift( )","learned":1},{"question":"How to make shallow copy of an array?","answer":"arr1 = [1,2,3,4,5]; arr2 = arr1.slice( );","learned":1},{"question":"Method to delete the last element of an array?","answer":"Array.prototype.pop( )","learned":1},{"question":"Method to delete first element of an array?","answer":"Array.prototype.push( )","learned":1},{"question":"How to use the properties and methods of a parent class in the child class constructor?","answer":"By calling the super( ) method with the required property or method as parameter.","learned":1},{"question":"Is Array.prototype.shift( ) chain-able with other array methods?","answer":"No. Because it returns the element that it removes from the given array and does not return any reference to the array itself.","learned":1},{"question":"Is JavaScript a loosely typed language?","answer":"Yes. Variables data types do not need to be defined and can change during runtime.","learned":1},{"question":"Is JavaScript similar to Java ?","answer":"Yes. JavaScript borrows a lot of syntax and semantics from Java. However, they are two completely different languages and not the same.","learned":1},{"question":"Is JavaScript just a front-end scripting language?","answer":"Yes. Vanilla JavaScript is just a front-end scripting language. However, with implementations like as Node.js, it can easily be used on the server-side.","learned":1},{"question":"How is React different from Angular ?","answer":"React is a library which allows easy DOM manipulation and View state control whereas Angular is a full fledged framework which integrates and manages the Model and View logic allowing flow of information between them.","learned":1},{"question":"What is a Map ?","answer":"Map is a new data structure introduced in ES2015 which is similar to Objects in that it stores data in a key:value format, but different in that it can use Objects as keys instead of just Object names as string keys.","learned":1},{"question":"What are rest parameters?","answer":"Introduced in ES2015, rest parameters allow values in an iterative data structure to be passed as discrete arguments to a function or method. Ex. let arr = [\"javascript\", \"script.js\", 55, 3]; getScript(...arr);","learned":1},{"question":"How to easily swap values of two variables?","answer":"[a, b] = [b, a]","learned":1},{"question":"Which method of the Object prototype can be overridden to set the primitive value of an object ?","answer":"valueOf( )","learned":1},{"question":"React and Angular are open source projects by which two companies?","answer":"Facebook and Google.","learned":1}]}];

